龙虾
变形室
我真的很抱歉
I'm really sorry
他是戴着框架眼镜还是隐形眼镜
Does he wear glasses or contact lens?
框架眼镜
Glasses
你要抓紧时间了
You would have to hurry up
他觉得穿这双棕色皮鞋最合适
He decided his brown leather shoes were the best pair to wear
他背部有些疼痛 但不同于以往...
His back hurt a little, but not like some other time in the past...
不再是那种难以忍受的疼痛
when the pain was intolerable
他心想 妻子早已不再爱他
He was thinking his wife doesn't love him at all anymore
他没有因此痛哭流涕 也没有想到
He didn't burst into tear and he didn't think...
当被爱人抛弃时
things most people do...
大部分人的第一反应 是哭泣
when they realise someone doesn't love them anymore is cry
先生 您能看向这边的镜头吗
Sir, would you mind take a look into the camera here for me?
好了 谢谢
That's ok, thank you
- 您之前单身过吗 - 不 从来没有
- Have you ever been on your own before? - No, never
- 对什么食物过敏吗 - 不
- Are you allergic to any food? - No
上一段感情持续了多少年
Your last relationship last how many years?
大概十二年
Around 12
- 您记得具体是多久吗 - 十一年七个月
- Do you remember how long exactly sir? - Eleven years and seven months
- 您的性取向是 - 异性恋
- Sexual preference?- Women
不过之前在大学的时候
However I had one homosexual experience...
有过一段同性恋的经历
in the past, in college
可以写成双性恋吗
Is there bisexual option available?
不能 先生 出于具体操作原因
No sir, this option is no longer available
从去年夏天开始
since about last summer...
就不能这么写了
due to several operational problems
恐怕您现在就要决定
I'm afraid you have yo decide right now if you want to be registered as...
以何种取向登记
homosexual or heterosexual
那就以异性恋登记吧
I think I should be registered as heterosexual
- 有小孩吗 先生 - 没有
- Any children sir?- No
那这只狗是
And dog?
那是我哥哥 他几年前来过这 但他没能成功
My brother, he was here couple of years ago, but he didn't make it
你也许记得他
You might remember him
中等身材 四十八岁 有些秃顶 金发
Medium built, 48 years old, bald patch, blond hair
恐怕我不太记得了 先生
I'm afraid no sir
好了 请在这张表上清楚得写下您的姓名
Ok, I like you to write your name clearly on this form
全部大写 并签上名字
In capital letter and sign please
很好 谢谢
Very good, thank you very much
您不能使用排球场地和网球场
So, you're not allow to use volley-ball or tennis court
这些仅供情侣使用
These are only for the couples
您可以使用单人的运动设施
You can use facility for individual sports
例如壁球和高尔夫
such as squash and golf
您最多可以在酒店住四十五天
You can stay at hotel for up to 45 days
您的房间是单人间
You would be staying at the single room
如果一切顺利并且成功找到伴侣
If everything goes well and you make it,
您可以搬去双人间
you would be moved to a double room
非常抱歉 您不能保留任何个人物品
I'm afraid you can't keep any of your personal belongings
我们会提供所有您需要的物品
We will provide everything you need as far as...
例如 衣物 饰品 鞋子等等
garments, accessories, and shoes are concerned
- 这个您可以留着 - 谢谢
- You can keep this - Thank you
- 请问您穿多大的鞋 - 四十四码半
- Shoe size please - 44 and a half
四十四还是四十五 这里没有半码的鞋子
44 or 45? there's no half sizes
四十五
如果您需要理发 请提前一天告知前台
If you need a hair cut, call reception one day ahead,
酒店内禁止吸烟
smoking is not allowed
这样能保证在狩猎时有充足的体能
That you would be able to run for longer during the hunt without getting tired...
以及亲吻时不会有口气
and you breath won't smell when you kiss
入住愉快
Enjoy your stay
不好意思
Excuse me
如果要理发 必须提前一天通知前台 是吗
If we need to get hair cut, we must call reception a day before, is that right?
- 是的 - 好的
- That's right - Great
他的房间号是101
His room number was 101
他床头的墙上
A tranqulizer gun...
挂着一把麻醉枪
was hanging on the wall above his bed
在桌上放着二十支麻醉镖
On the table were 20 tranquilzer darts...
一块黑色的塑料手表 一副太阳镜
a black plastic watch, a pair of sunglasses...
以及男士古龙香水
and a cologne for man
衣柜里是四条款式一样的灰色裤子
Inside the wardrobe were four identical grey trousers...
四件扣紧的男士衬衫  蓝白两色
four identical button down shirts in white and blue...
一条皮带 一双袜子 一条内裤 一件夹克衫
a belt, socks, underwear, a blazer...
一根条纹领带和一件白色浴袍
a striped tie and a white bathrobe
他看向窗外
He looked out of window
被捕的独身者们
The unconscious bodies of captured loners...
毫无知觉地躺在湿漉漉的地上
were lying on the wet ground
"幸好他们穿着防水的斗篷" 他心想
"Thank God they wear those water proof ponchos", he thought
195房
Room 195
捕到两个独身者 赢得额外的两天时间
Two loners, two extra days
272房
Room 272
捕到一个独身者 赢得额外的一天
One loner, one extra day
你好 我是酒店经理 这位先生是我的伴侣
Hello, I'm the hotel manager, and this gentleman is my partner
我们在此欢迎您入住
We like to welcome you
您是住客中的幸运儿
You're one of the lucky one
您的房间有我们这最好的景致
You have one of our supreme room which means you have a view
- 您看过宣传手册了吗 - 是的
- Did you read the lease list - Yes it is
很好
Very good
在您入住的这段期间 如果没有找到伴侣
Now the fact you turning into a animal...
你将变成一种动物
if you fail to fall in love with someone during your stay here...
但你不必因此感到焦虑和沮丧
is not something should upset you or get you down
既是变成了动物
Just think as a animal...
您也有第二次的机会找到伴侣
you have a second chance to find a companion
当然 您要仔细考虑
But even then you must be careful
您得找到一个相近的物种
You need to choose a companion that is similar type animal...
作为伴侣
to you
毕竟 狼和企鹅可是永远无法共处的
A wolf and a penguin can never live together
骆驼和河马也一样
Nor a camel and a hippopotamus
否则就会太荒谬了 您觉得呢
That would be absurd, think about it
我理解 这种谈话可能让您不太舒服
I understand this discussion is a little unpleasant for you
但我的职责就是
But it is my duty to prepare you...
让你做好心理准备 去迎接所有可能的结果
psychologically for all possible outcomes
那么如果您在结束前没能找到伴侣
Now have you thought of what animal you like to be
您想变成什么动物呢
if end up alone?
我想变成一只龙虾
Yes, a lobster
为什么是龙虾呢
Why a lobster?
因为龙虾可以活一百多年
Because lobster live for over one hundred years
其蓝色血液有着贵族的气息
Are blue blood like aristocrat...
而且终生保持生育能力
and stay fertile all their life
我也很喜欢大海
I also like the sea very much
我年轻时就很擅长滑水和游泳
I water ski, swim quite well since I was a teenager
我必须恭喜您 大多数人第一个想到的是狗
I must congratulate you, the first thing most people think of is a dog...
这就是为什么满世界都是狗
which is why the world is full of dogs
很少有人选择不同寻常的动物...
Very few people choose unusual animal...
这也是为什么他们正在濒临灭绝
which is why they are in danger
龙虾是极好的选择
A lobster is a excellent choice
您能站起来一下吗
Could you stand for us please?
这是为了让您明白
This is to show you how easy life is...
相比形单影只 成双成对会过得更舒适
when there are two of something rather than just one
我们总是时常忘记
We tend to forget that from time to time
明天这个时候您就能把手铐取下来了
The handcuff will be removed the same time tomorrow
抱歉 鲍勃
I'm sorry bob
希望我们能相处愉快
Hope you enjoy staying with us
再见
Goodbye
祝您一天愉快
Have a good day
早上好
Good morning
101房间 剩余四十四天
Room 101, 44 days left
早餐已开始供应
Breakfast is served
他永远不会忘记在酒店的第一天
His first day was one he never forget
他旁边的桌子坐着一个年轻的女人
Near his table of breakfast sat a young women...
她的头向后仰着
with her head tilted back
后来他会知道
Later he would learn...
原来她经常流鼻血
she often got nose bleed
她边上坐着她最好的朋友
Next to her sat her best friend
他对倒咖啡的侍者表示感谢
He thanked the waiter who served his coffee...
并想起了他的妻子
and thought about his wife for a moment
有个女人似乎很喜欢黄油饼干
A woman who seems to like butter biscuit...
她把饼干给了一个喝着
offered one to a man drinking...
金巴利苏打的男人当做早餐
a Compari soda for breakfast
之后他回头看到了一个女人
He then looked behind him saw a woman...
之后他会知道 这女人是多么铁石心肠
who would later find out was absolutely heartless
还看到了一些情侣区的人
And some others in the couple's area...
在他入住期间 或许永远不会遇到这些人
whom he may never meet druing his stay at the hotel
那个早上他真的很饿
That morning he was really hungry
饿到能够吃下一整只鸡
He could eat a whole chicken...
但他几乎没吃什么东西
but ate almost nothing
- 你好 - 你好
- Hello - Hello
我要和我的新朋友去外面散个步
I decided to go for a walk ouside with my new friend
我来为你介绍一下
Let me introduce you
这是罗伯特 住在我隔壁 说话有点口齿不清
This is Robert, he stay in the room next to mine had a lisp
很高兴认识你 我住在101房
Please to meet you, I stay in the room 101
我住同一层楼 186房
I'm on the same floor, 186
- 想和我们一起去走走吗 - 可以啊
- Would you like to join us?- Why not
总有一天我会坐上那游艇
One of these days gonna be me on one of those yachts
为什么
Why those yachts?
在你走之前会有个最后的考验
The final ordeal before letting you go
最难的一关
The hardest one
十五天的假期 情侣单独共处
15 days of vacation just a couple alone,
你没有看过宣传手册吗
Ddn't you read the leaflet?
我看了
I did
你看过约翰的腿了吗
Did you see John's leg?
没有
No
约翰 让我们看看你的腿
John, could you show your leg?
好吧
Oh yeah
有请187房 今天是他入住的第二天
Room 187, day 2
大家好
Hello everyone
当我父亲爱上了另一个女人的时候
My mother was left on her own
他抛弃了我的母亲
when my father fell in love with a woman...
只是因为她数学比我母亲好
who was better at math than she was
我想 她有研究生的学历
She has postgraduate degree, I think
然而我母亲只是个本科生
While my mother only a graduate
当时我十九岁
I was 19 at the time
我母亲来过这家酒店 但没能成功找到伴侣
My mother entered the hotel but didn't make it
最后变成了一只狼
and was turning into a wolf
我很想念她
I really miss her
后来我得知她被送到了一家动物园
I found out she's been moved to a zoo
我经常跑去看她
I often went there to see her
我给她喂生肉吃
I give her raw meat
我知道狼喜欢生肉
I knew the wolf like raw meat
但我不知道到底哪只狼是我的母亲
But I couldn't figure out which of the wolves was my mother
所以我会给每只狼都喂一点
So I used to give a little bit to each of them
有天 我决定闯入围栏
One day I decided to enter the enclosure
因为我真的很想念她 想拥抱她
I really missed her and I wanted a hug
我翻过并跳进了围栏
I climbed the fence and jumped in
群狼立即朝我冲来  围攻我
All the wolves charged at once and attacked me
只有两只狼纹丝不动
All but two stood motionless
于是我推断 其中一头必是我母亲
I guess one of those two must be my mother
动物园的警卫迅速地救了我 把我送去了医院
The zoo guard got to me quite quickly and took me to the hospital
谢天谢地 我保住了我的腿
Thankfully I didn't lose my leg
只是有些瘸而已
I just had this limp
这也随之成为了我的标志性特征
Which also is my defining characteristic
我的妻子在六天前去世了
My wife died six days ago
她很漂亮 我也很爱她
She was very beautiful and I love her very much
她也有些瘸
She had limp too
谢谢 约翰 回到自己的座位上吧
Thank you John, you can return to you seat
下一位客人 104房 第二天
Let's move on to our next guest, room 104, day 2
大家好
Hello everyone
这只是我入住的第二天
This is only my second day here
但我感到自己成功的融入了这个大家庭
But already I feel like a member of wonderful group
我的标志性特征是 我有着美丽的笑容
My defining characteristic is that I have very beautiful smile
# 有东西抓住了我的心 #
#Something's gotten hold of my heart#
# 让我疯狂 让我神志不清 #
#Keeping my soul and my senses apart#
# 有东西闯入了我的生活 #
#Something's gotten into my life#
你有和别人跳过舞吗
Have you ever dance with anybody?
什么
Sorry?
你和别人一起跳过舞吗
Have you ever dance with anybody?
跳过
Yes
跳的是什么类型舞呢
What sort of dancing you should do?
这根据音乐而定
Just depends on the music
你要坐下来吗
Do you need to sit down?
不 不 我打算去跳舞
No, no, I'm getting ready to dance
我能坐这吗
Can I sit here?
抱歉
I'm sorry
- 我能坐这吗 - 当然
- Can I sit here? Of course
我来给你介绍下我的好朋友
Let me introduce you to my best friend
刚才和你聊天那个女人是个很冷漠的人
That woman you were talking to have no feeling whatsoever
她对什么都不感兴趣
She feels nothing at all
她是酒店里最好的猎手
She's the best hunter in hotel
悄无声息 却身手敏捷
Silent and very fast
她是女子记录保持者
She's the women record holder
总共捕获了一百九十二个孤独者
192 captors
# 抹去了灰色 抹去了蓝色 #
#Changing the grey, changing the blue#
# 为我涂上鲜红 #
# Scarlet for me...#
# 为你而靓丽 #
#it's scarlet for you#
# 我想知道这是否真实 #
#if this is the real thing#
能赏脸跳一支舞吗
Would you like to dance?
# 每一天 耶 #
#Every day yeah#
# 当你触碰我时 我已迷失了自我 #
#You touch me and my mind goes astray yeah#
# 宝贝 宝贝 #
#And baby, and Baby#
#宝贝 宝贝 #
# 有东西抓住了我的心 #
#Something's gotten hold of my heart#
# 指引我的灵魂到了仙境 #
#Dragging my soul to a beautiful land#
# 有东西闯入我的生活 #
#Something's gotten into my life#
很抱歉 我把血滴到了你的衬衫上
I'm sorry, I got the blood on your shirt
但别担心 去掉血渍的方法有很多
But don't worry, there are many ways to remove blood stain from clothing
一种方法是把衣服用冷水拧干
One way is to wring the clothes to cold water,
然后用海盐搓洗
then rub in sea salt
另一种方法是用沾有氨水的棉棒擦掉血渍
Another way is to srape the stain with cotton ball dip in ammonia
第三种方法是将面粉团做成牙膏状
The third way is to make flour mold into a paste like toothpaste
尤其适用于贵重衣物以及亮色衣服
Especially it the clothes are delicate or bright color
但千万别用温水去洗血渍
But juse never use warm water on blood, ever
好的
Ok
# 但是 你 你 你 #
But then you, you, you#
# 你向我走来 #
You came my way#
# 但你朝我走来 #
#But then you came my way#
# 一种莫名的感觉涌上心头 #
#And a feeling unknown shook my heart...#
# 让我想与你 #
make me want you to stay
# 日日夜夜不分离 #
#all of my nights and all of my days#
我想去休息下
I think I have to rest for a little bit
- 我腿有点痛 - 没关系 去吧
- My leg hurts - That's ok
等你好些的时候告诉我 我们能继续跳
But let me know when you feel better, and we can dance again
# 让我疯狂 让我失去了理智 #
Keeping my soul and my senses apart
# 有东西侵入了我的夜晚 #
#Something has invaded my light#
# 用亮色涂满了我的梦境 #
#Painting my sleep with the colours so bright#
# 改变了灰暗 改变了蓝色 #
#Changing the gray changing the blue#
# 为我涂上了鲜红 #
#Scarlet for me#
# 为你而靓丽 #
#it's scarlet for you#
请大家有序退场
Leave the building in orderly fashion
动作迅速 但请小心脚下
Do hurry up, and please be carefully
注意不要受伤
no one should get hurt or injured...
祝大家捕猎好运
and good luck with the hunt
我真希望我的腿没有瘸
I wish I didn't have this limp
我曾今很擅长跑步 但现在不太可能了
I used to good at running, but not anymore
我很确信我会比其他人慢
I'm sure would be slower than them
如果我是你 我会想些别的致胜技巧
If I were you, I think of some trick that choose element of surprise...
而不是靠速度取胜
instead of speed
你说得对
You're right
我应该如此
That's what I would do
# 在你还爱我的时候回头 #
#Back when you loved me#
# 有天早上你问过我 #
#You asked me one morning while we were talking#
# 生活是什么 #
#"what was life about?"#
# 我对你说 对有些人来说生活是酒 #
#I turned and told you for some it's the wine#
# 对有些人来说 生活是荣耀 #
#for some it's the glory#
# 对有些人来说 生活是为了致富 #
#for some it's being rich#
# 但对我来说 你才是我生活的意义 #
#but for me it is only you#
# 对有些人来说 生活是荣耀 #
#for some it's the glory#
# 对有些人来说 生活是为了致富 #
#for some it's being rich#
# 但对我来说 你才是我生活的意义 #
#but for me it is only you#
# 但你的心已然改变 #
#Now that your heart has changed#
# 你爱上了别人 #
#And you love someone else#
# 你还是想知道生活的意义 #
#You still wonder what they're saying#
# 我的心很痛 #
#How my own heart beats#
# 是否还有像我这样的人存在 #
#Are there perhaps more people like me exist#
# 心早已心如死灰 #
#Dead on the inside#
# 人却随波逐流 #
#Alive on the outside#
# 心早已心如死灰 #
#Dead on the inside#
# 人却随波逐流 #
#Alive on the outside#
186房
Room 186
捕到一个孤独者 赢得额外的一天
One loner, one extra day
剩余三十八天 加上一天 一共三十九天
38 days left, plus one, 39
180房
Room 180
剩余天数不变
The day of your stay remain unchanged
290房
Room 290
捕到四个孤独者 赢得额外的四天
Four loners, four extra days
剩一百五十四天 加上四天 共一百五十八天
154 days left, plus four, 158
101房
Room 101
剩余天数不变
The day of your stay remain unchanged
剩余三十二天
32 days left
早餐已开始供应
Breakfast is served
男人独自吃饭
Man eats alone
- 你昨天用了多少枚镖 - 十二枚
- How many darts did you use yesterday? - 12
请脱掉你的裤子 坐在床上
Please take off your trousers and sit on the bed
我们今天能不做这个吗
Can we not do this today?
感觉很难受
It's awful
我知道 但恐怕我们必须做
I know, but I'm afraid we have to do it
您要知道 这能够在心理层面帮助到您...
And you have no idea how much it help you psychologically...
寻找伴侣
in your search for partner
男女共餐
Man eats with woman
躺下
Lie down.
把腿张开一点
Spread your legs. More.
- 你是住在186房吗 - 正是
- ls your room number 186?- Yes it is
我想您应该知道 在这个酒店内的任何地方
I imagine you know masturbation is not permitted
自慰都是被严令禁止的吧
in the room or any other area of the hotel
是的
Yes
但是 我发现您还是有自慰的行为
And yet, it is been brought to my attention you continue to do it
今天你比以往勃起得都要快 这很好
Today, you became erect quicker than other days, that's good
求求你 再久一点
Please, just a little longer
祝您有愉快的一天
Have a good day
这感觉很难受 真的很难受
That's awful, just awful
您自慰的时候有看图片吗
Are you looking at the photograph while you masturbating?
有看
Yes
图片上面是什么
What does the photograph show?
一个在乡间骑马的裸女
A naked woman on a horse in the country
如果我是你
If I were in your shoes
我不会注意看那个裸女 而是会注意那匹马
I would not be ogling the naked woman but the horse.
我敢说 那匹马也曾经和你一样
I'm sure that horse's once a weak and cowardly man...
是个懦夫
just like you.
女人独自走路时
Woman walks alone.
救命
Help!
没有这个必要 求你了
This is not necessary, please...
那只是个意外 我只是有点昏头了
It was a accident, I just got carried away.
没有这个必要
This is not necessary.
请把手放在面包机上
Please place your hand on the toaster.
只用警告我就好
This could be a warning.
我一直表现良好 我...
I've been good otherwise, I...
我错了
I'm sorry.
我错了 求你了
I'm sorry, please.
求你了 我认错了
Please, please, I'm sorry.
女人和男人一起走路
Woman walks with man.
一旦你进入那个房间
What they do as soon as you enter the room...
会先把你的全身彻底清洗一遍
is to wash you body and your head really well.
你怎么知道
How did you know?
我叔叔曾经认识这里的一名服务生
My uncle used to know a waiter who worked here.
服务生怎么会知道流程
The waiter know the procedure?
他们是不被允许进入那个房间的
They are not allow to inside that room.
不管怎样 接下来他们会剥去你的皮
Nevertheless, they peel off the skin...
经过水洗和肥皂之后 皮肤已经变软了
which has become soft due to the watering and soap.
之后 他们会用激光或手术刀摘除心脏 眼球
Afterward they remove the heart, the eyes and other vital organs of the body...
以及其它重要器官
with laser or scalpels.
根据所选的动物不同 之后的流程也不尽相同
Then the procedure changes according to the animal one has choosen.
你说的很有道理
That makes total sense.
我猜测 比如哺乳动物和飞禽的步骤
I mean I suppose mammals demand different kind of work than...
- 就会大不相同 - 的确
- fowl, for example. - Exactly.
之后他们会把尸体残骸
Afterward they throw remaining body parts of
扔在酒店餐厅外面
the carcass outside the hotel restaurant...
血液则供给市里的医院
and distribute the blood to the hospital in the city.
为什么
Why is that?
这些血液可以供给献血不足的地区做手术
The blood is used for surgery where there aren't blood donor available.
- 昨天有新人入住 - 我看到了
- New guests arrived yesterday. - Yes I saw them.
我好像看到了一个瘸腿的女人
I think I saw a woman with limp.
她只是扭伤了脚踝
It is just sprained ankle.
几天之后 她就会恢复正常了
She would be walking normally again after a few days.
真可惜
That's a shame.
的确很可惜
It's a shame indeed.
有一晚在大巴上
One night on the coach,
他坐在那个喜欢奶油饼干的女人身边
he sat next to woman who like butter biscuit.
他盯着窗外 不是为了看什么
He gazed out of the window, not looking at anything in particular.
只是为了避免跟她交谈
Just trying avoid talking to her.
- 鲍勃怎么样 - 它没事
- How is Bob? - He is fine.
我真想和你与鲍勃一起在午后散步
Give anything to go for a walk with you and Bob one afternoon.
恐怕狗不能外出 这是规定
The dogs are not allow. There's a rule, I'm afraid.
他想 "总有些让人无法反驳的借口"
"There are some excuses no one can't argue with", he thought.
毋庸置疑 借口有好坏之分
Some excuses without a doubt better than others.
而刚才那个借口就很好
That was really good one.
这些饼干是给鲍勃的
These biscuits are for Bob.
如果你想奖励它 可以把这个给它
I want you to give them to him whenever you want to reward him for something.
- 告诉它这是我送的 - 谢谢
- Tell him it is from me - Thank you.
什么时候我能去你房间聊天吗
Can I come to your room sometime for a chat.
我可以给你吹箫
I could give you a blow job.
或者你也可以直接上我
Or you could just fuck me.
吹箫时我总会吞下去的
I always swallow after fellatio and absolutely
如果你喜欢肛交也绝对没问题
have no problem with anal sex if that's you thing.
我的前夫总是说
My ex-husband always used to said that
我的身材是他见过最好的 但还是不说他了
I have the most beautiful size he's ever see, but let's not talk about him.
我的房间号是180 所以分机号也是180
My room number is 180, so my telephone extension is 180.
希望今晚能抓到些独身者吧
Hope catch some loners tonight.
前几个晚上一个都没有抓到
Haven't caught any the last few nights.
也希望你能抓到很多
Hope you catch lots too.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
如果我不能很快找到合适的伴侣
If I don't find a suitable partner soon,
我就打算跳楼自杀
I'm gonna kill myself by throwing myself out of one of room.
从窗户上跳下去
Out the window.
我希望你能记住
I want you to know that
我的房间在一楼
my room is on the first floor.
"我希望今晚能抓到独身者"
"I hope catch some loners today"...
她说道
she said.
"也希望你能找到很多"
"And I hope you catch lots too".
她接着告诉他 如果她不能
She then told him that if she didn't...
很快找到合适的伴侣
find suitable partner soon,
就会从某个房间的窗户上跳下去自杀
She was going to kill herself by jumping from one of room windows.
也许是320房间
320, maybe.
或者更高点 480房间 这样更合适
Or one higher up, 480, that would be even better.
她说完后
When she stop talking,
他茫然地盯着她 无言以对
He stare at her blankly, not knowing what to say.
接着他看向森林 再一次想到
He then look out of the woods, thought once more...
他的借口有多棒
how good his excuse's been.
不错 再高一点
Not bad, a bit higher.
如果失败了 你有想过变成什么动物吗
You thought about what animal you wanna be if you don't make it?
一只龙虾
A lobster.
如果失败了 我想变成一只鹦鹉
I'm gonna be a parrot if I don't make it.
不如你也变成鹦鹉吧 我们就有伴了
Why don't you become parrot too, then we all be together?
你真是个白痴
You're complete idiot.
自己有语言障碍
Picking one of few animals that can talk...
还要选会说话的动物
when you have a speech impediment.
就算变成动物 你也还是口齿不清
You're lisp even as a animal.
至于你 他们会抓住你
As for you, they will catch you
把你扔进沸水里活活烫死
and put you in a pot of boiling water until you die.
接着会用工具撬开你的壳
And then crack open you claws with a tool by prying it,
用嘴吮吸那一丁点鲜肉
then suck up what little flesh you have with their mouth.
你们俩真是太可悲了
You're pathetic, both of you!
我才不会变成动物 但到时候会带着我的伴侣
I'm not gonna be turning into some animal, I'll come visit you though...
去看望你们的 之后我们会去公园
with my patner, then we walking together in some park of...
会去旅行 会去海里游泳
where we swimming in the sea when we're on one of our trip.
朋友
Friends!
187号房间 请过来
Room 187, please.
靶纸的形状是单身而非情侣 这不是巧合
It's not coincidence that targets are shape like single people and not couples.
你好
Hello.
- 你好 - 你的泳衣真漂亮
- Hello. - You swimsuit is very nice.
- 谢谢 - 不客气
- Thank you very much. - You're welcome.
你喜欢蛙泳 自由泳 蝶泳还是仰泳
Do you like to swim breaststroke, front crawl, batterfly or backstroke?
我都喜欢
I like all sorts equally.
我喜欢蛙泳
You know I love breaststroke.
真的 我朋友总是取笑我 他们说
Oh really, my friends often teased me, said...
"别总是蛙泳了"
"stop swimming breaststroke all the time"...
之后他们就会笑
and they laughed.
蛙泳很好啊
Breaststroke is great.
可以很好地锻炼背部肌肉
It's excellent exercise for the back.
男人蛙泳时不应该穿泳裤
When swimming breaststroke, men shouldn't wear swimming shorts...
那会限制臀部的运动
has really limit movement in the buttocks.
不过你知道这个的 对吗
But you know that, didn't you?
你流鼻血了
I think your nose is bleeding.
真的吗
Really?
该死
Oh, no.
我总是这样
This happen to me all the time.
真的很烦人
It's really, really annoying.
我理解 我也有流鼻血的毛病
I know, I have nose bleeding problem too.
我看到你做了什么 一定很疼
I saw what you did, must have hurt.
鼻血出来了吗
Is it coming out?
没有
No.
现在流出来了
Yes.
- 给我点纸巾好吗 - 好的
- Can I use the tissue? - Yes.
我想问你一个问题 希望你能诚恳地回答
Can I ask you a question, I want you to answer me honestly.
哪一种情况更糟 是在森林里饥寒交迫而死
What's worse? to die of cold and hunger in the woods?
还是变成动物之后被天敌吃掉或者杀掉
To become a animal would be killed or eaten by some big animal?
或者还是时不时的流鼻血
Or have nose bleed from time to time?
变成动物之后被天敌吃掉或者杀掉 这更糟糕
To become a animal would be killed or eaten by some big animal.
没错
Exactly.
- 她没有怀疑你在作假吗 - 没有
- She isn't suspect you're lying? - No.
我很高兴 因为一对新情侣产生了
I'm very happy because we have a new couple.
他们于两天前相识
They met just two days ago.
但现在已经深爱彼此 琴瑟相谐
But they very much in love and perfect suited.
他们的鼻子都有同样的问题
They both have same problem with their noses.
会突然流鼻血
They bleed quite suddenly.
明天他们会换到双人间
Tomorrow they will be transfer to a double room...
那里有更大的衣柜和卫生间
with larger wardrobe and larger bathroom.
他们会在双人间里住两周
They will remain in the double room for two weeks...
之后会换到游艇上 再住两周
and then been transferred to the yacht for the further two weeks.
我们衷心祝福你们能成功
We wish you every success
最终以情侣的身份返回城市
and hope you return to the city as a couple.
- 我觉得非常幸福 - 我也是
- I'm very happy. - Me too.
恭喜
Congratulation.
我们的员工以及我本人将会密切监视
The course of your relationship will be monitored closely...
你们交往期间的感情状况
by our stuffs and by me personally.
如果你们遇到了任何不能自行解决
If you encounter any problems, any tensions, any arguing...
问题 矛盾 或是争吵
that you can't resolve yourselves,
我们会分配给你们孩子
You would be asign children.
通常那样就会解决很多问题
That usually helps a lot.
早上好
Good morning.
101房间 剩余七天
Room 101, 7 days left.
早餐已开始供应
Breakfast is served.
你的头发真好看
You have really nice hair.
我知道
I know.
你看
Look.
那你喜欢我的头发吗
How do you like mine?
我感觉你的发质有点干燥
I think yours quite dry hair.
颜色倒是不错
Color is ok though.
最重要的是你没有谢顶
The most important thing is that you're not bald.
可惜对于男人 谢顶总是不可避免
However when comes to men, bald is always the possibility you can't avoid.
- 你父亲谢顶了吗 - 他没有
- ls your father bald? - No he isn't.
即便哪天我秃顶了
And even if somedays I lose my hair,
也有办法让头发再生的
there are things I can do to get my hair back.
我可以去植发
I can have a hair transplant.
植发的人一眼就能被看穿
You always can tell someone had a hair transplant.
- 我知道 - 好头发并非人人都能拥有
- I know. - Nice hair is not something you can get
这是与生俱来的
It's something you born with.
你父亲没有谢顶 并不代表你就能松口气了
The fact your father isn't bald shouldn't put you at ease.
你想好最后一天会做什么了吗
Have you decided what you're going to do in your last day?
我还在考虑
I'm still thinking about it.
早上好 女士们
Morning ladies.
今天是你的最后一天
So, today is your last day.
按照惯例 你可以选择
And as the customary, you can choose...
如何度过最后一晚
how you like to spend your last night.
在这种情况下我都会建议你选择
What I always said in this situation is it would
变成动物后不能做到的事情
be wise to do something you can't do as animal.
例如读一部经典文学
For example read a work of classic literature...
或者唱一曲喜欢的歌
or sing a song you really like.
选择下面的这些事情就太傻了
It would be silly to choose...
比如 去野外散步
for example, a walking the ground...
或者和别人做爱
or have sex intercourse with another person,
这些变成动物后也能做的
those are things you can do as animal.
但首先 你最好的朋友有点东西
But first, your best friend is reading something...
她想和你分享 这真是太感人
she like to read you, it's really very touching.
在学校时我们总是坐在一起
We always sat together at school...
每当我有了麻烦
and whenever I had a problem...
我都向你倾诉 因为你总能给出最好的建议
I told you about it because you always give the best advice.
当我们在学校舞会上
When we didn't manage to find...
没能找到舞伴的时候
dance partner at the school prom,
我们患难与共 这给予我力量
The fact we were together at that difficult moment give me strength.
我很抱歉事情到了现在的局面
I'm sorry things come to this.
我确信如果能再多给你几天
I'm sure if you have a few more days
你一定能像我样找到伴侣
you would find someone just like I did,
因为你是如此可爱
because you're a adorable person...
拥有美丽的秀发和清新的口气
and you have very beautiful hair and very nice breath.
我一直很嫉妒你的秀发
I'm always jealous of your hair...
你知道的
you know that.
不论过去 现在 还是将来
You were, are, and always
你都是我最好的朋友
will be my best friend
我会时常想念你 我会永远带着生日时
And I'll think of you often, and I'll always wear those silver earing...
你送我的银耳环
you give me for my birthday
我会想你的
I'll miss you
无论我将来回到城市里
And However many new girl friends I make in a few days...
会结交多少新闺蜜
when I move back into the city,
我都不会再找到你这样真实...
I don't think I'll find another as true...
我想独自看那部电影"伴我同行"
I like to ask for the film "Stand By Me"...
由瑞凡・菲尼克斯 基弗・萨瑟兰
with River Phoenix, Kiefer Sutherland...
和理查德・德莱福斯主演的那部
and Richard Dreyfuss, alone.
明智的选择
Excellent choice.
很不错的电影
Lovely film.
请留言
Please leave a message
你好
Hello
你可能在浴室吧 所以听不到电话响
You're probably in the bathroom, that's why you can't hear phone ring.
早上洗个冷水澡真是再舒服不过了
Nothing like a cold shower in the morning.
等你洗完澡我再打给你
Well, I'll call you a little bit later after you finish your shower.
稍后再聊
We'll talk later.
再见
Bye.
一天 当他打高尔夫球时
One day, as he was playing golf,
他意识到 没有情感时却装作感情充沛
he thought that it is more difficult to pretend
要比有情感时装作冷漠无情
you do have feelings when you don't...
要更为艰难
than to pretend you don't have feelings when you do.
他也想到 他其实喜欢她的口音
He also thought that he like her accent.
而且他总是偏爱短发女人
and he always prefer woman with short hair.
于是他认定她就是自己要找的伴侣
So he decided she was the one.
捕猎时 他会跟着她
During the hunt, he would followed her.
一旦她击中了某个独身者 他就会对她说
And as soon as she shot a loner, he would said to her:
"真希望我们用的是真枪
"I wish we have real gun...
而非这些愚蠢的麻醉枪
instead of this silly tranquilizer one...
不如你徒手杀了他吧"
why don't you kill him with your bare hands?"
当她掐住独身者的喉咙时
And the moment she put her hand around loner's throat,
他就会说
He would said:
"希望他能马上死去"
"I hope him die right the way".
出什么事了
What happened?
她从180房间的窗户上跳了下去
She jumped from the window of room 180.
到处都是血迹和饼干
There are bloods and biscuits everywhere.
希望她能马上死去
I hope she die right the way.
转念一想 我还是希望她能在死前多受点折磨
On second thought, I hope she suffers quite a bit before she dies
我只希望在我的房间里
I just hope her pathetic scream...
听不到她可悲的嘶喊
can't be heard from my room.
因为我正想休息一会儿 需要安宁
Because I was thinking about having a lie down and I need peace and quiet.
我刚打完高尔夫 很累了
I was playing golf and I'm quite tired.
我可不希望听到一个女人死前还不停地哭嚎
The last thing I need is some woman dying slowly and loudly.
她喊的这么大声 我听不到你说什么
I can't hear you with all this screaming.
我们另找个安静的时间再聊吧
We'll talk some other time when it's quieter.
再见
Good bye.
一条留言
One message
你好
Hello.
你可能在浴室吧 所以听不到电话响
You're probably in the bathroom, that's why you can't hear phone ring.
早上洗个冷水澡真是再舒服不过了
Nothing like a cold shower in the morning.
等你洗完澡我再打给你
Well, I'll call you a little bit later after you finish your shower.
稍后再聊
We'll talk later.
再见
Bye.
介意我坐过来和你一起吗
Do you mind if I join in?
你喜欢马提尼酒是吗
You like Martini?
- 我觉得咱俩很般配 - 我也这么认为
- I think we're a match. - Yes, I think so too.
这是双人间的钥匙
The keys to the double room, please.
我和酒店全体同仁衷心祝你们幸福美满
I wish you the best of the luck, we all wish you the best of the luck
你通常睡在床的左边还是右边
Do you normally sleep on the left side of the bed or the right?
- 右边 你呢 - 左边 太好了
- The right, you? - The left, perfect
打开双腿
Spread your legs.
需要我关灯吗 还是你想读会书
Should I shut off the light or would you like to read?
- 我想读书 灯光会影响你吗 - 不会
- I'd like to read, does light bother you? - No
我睡觉不会受灯光和噪声的影响
I'm not bothered by light or noise.
我睡觉很沉
I'm deep sleeper.
- 你们好 - 你们好
- Hello. - Hello.
- 恭喜你们 - 谢谢
- Congratulation. - Thank you.
这是我们的新女儿 名叫伊丽莎白
This is our new daughter, her name is Elizabeth.
伊丽莎白 快去亲亲叔叔 他是我的朋友
Elizabeth, give this nice man a kiss, he is a friend of mine.
我最不喜欢就是傻姑娘的亲吻
The last thing I want right now is a kiss from silly little girl.
拜托 你知道的
Come on, you know.
哭什么 你应该感谢我 伊丽莎白
Don't cry, you should thank me, Elizabeth.
现在你的腿瘸了 更像你爸爸了
Now you have a limp and would be more like your father.
那个声音是什么
What was that sound?
你说什么了吗
Did you say something?
没有
No.
介意换个姿势吗 好让我看着你的脸
Do you mind if we fuck in a position where I can see your face?
好的
Sure.
打开灯吧 这样我才可以看到你
Turn the light on please,so I can see you better.
早安
Good morning.
我杀了你的兄弟
I killed your bother.
让他慢慢死去
I left him to die very slowly.
我们说话的时候 他可能还没死透
He may not be dead yet as now we speak.
我踢了他很久
I was kicking him for ages.
无所谓
Doesn't matter.
他发出了奇怪的哀号声 像这样
He whined a little the strangest kind of bark, something like this.
他一定很痛苦
Must have been from pain.
- 你什么也没有听到吗 - 没有
- You didn't hear anything? - No.
你的确睡得很沉
You really are deep sleeper.
- 你想喝咖啡吗 - 太好了
- Would you like some coffee? - I love some
等我刷牙洗脸完后
As soon as I wash my face and brush my teeth.
我等不及想听 昨晚你答应要讲给的故事了
I can't wait to hear that story you promise to tell me last night...
关于大学里你的那个学生
about that student of yours in the university,
以及他糟糕的期末项目
and his awful final project.
这个故事确实很有趣
It's really very funny story.
那个学生叫瑞斯
His name is Ryess.
祥瑞的瑞 宙斯的斯 瑞斯
R-y-e-s-s, Ryess.
这不是眼泪 只是水滴 我刚才在洗脸
It is not tear, just water, I just washed my face.
我就知道你在撒谎
I knew you were lying.
我不明白你为什么这样做
I can't understand why you did it.
所有人都清楚
When you know as anyone...
情侣关系是不能建立在谎言之上
that relationship can not be built on the lie.
我们马上去见酒店经理 你会得到应有的惩罚
We're going to the hotel manager right now, and you'll get the punishment you deserve.
这会受到什么惩罚
What's the punishment for this?
他们会把你变成没人想变成的动物
They turn you into animal no one wants to be.
我看到你的伴侣从那条路走了
I saw you partner went back that way.
他看起来很慌乱
He looked frantic.
一切都还好吗
Is everything ok?
起初他想让她在受尽折磨而死
At first he wanted to kill her in some horrible and painful way...
就像她对他兄弟做的那样
like the death she inflicted on his brother.
他考虑过不停地踢她的胃部
He thought about kicking her in the stomach over and over again.
然后在同样部位再捅上几刀
And then stabbing her in the same spot in the stomach.
但他又觉得这是徒劳 因为她已经不省人事了
Then he thought there wouldn't be much point because she's already unconscious...
感觉不到踢打或者刀插的痛苦
and wouldn't feel any pain from the kick or the knife.
你也得向我开一枪
You have to shoot me,
这样他们就不会怀疑我帮了你
so they don't suspect I helped you.
一名酒店服女佣帮了他
A hotel maid helped him.
他不知道为什么她要这么做
He couldn't understand why she did it
他决定把她转化为一只动物
So he decided to turn her into a animal
他把她拖进了变形室
He dragged her to the room with transformation took place
我问过他很多次 他究竟把她变成了什么动物
I asked him many times what sorts of animal he turn her into
但他总是用同样的答案回答我
But he always give me the same answer
"这跟你无关"
"That's none of your concern"
那晚他离开了酒店
That night he left the hotel...
彻底地离开了
once and for all
他开始漫无目的地跑着
He began to run without knowing where he was headed
但其实他是朝我们跑来的
But he was headed towards us
这是他新生命的起点
This was the start of his new life
那时候 他还不知道孤独是多么痛苦
Back then, he didn't know how much it hurts to be alone
也不知道当背部一直疼痛难忍
How much it hurts when you can not reach to rub pain relieve ointment on your back
却无法自己上药的痛苦
And you're constantly in pain
在森林里找到的他 是从酒店逃出来的
Find him in the woods, he escaped from hotel
你是医生吗
Are you a doctor by any chance?
不是
No
真可惜
That's a pity
我们这里需要一名医生
We need a doctor around
我们曾有过名医生 但他们几个月前抓住了他
We had one, but they caught him a couple of months ago
我是一名建筑师
I'm a architect
那也不错 欢迎加入
That's ok, so welcome
只要你愿意 你可以一直和我们待在一起
You can stay with us for as long as you like
你可以到死都是个独身者 没有时间限制
You can be a loner until the day you die, there is no time limit
非常感谢
Thank you very much
不过 在独身者与独身者之间
Anyway, any romantic or sexual relations...
任何感情或是性关系都是不允许的
between loners are not permitted
任何相关的举措都会被严惩 清楚了吗
And any such acts are punished, is that clear?
我能和别人聊天吗
Can I have a converstation with someone?
当然可以 只要不含调情或类似的含义就行
Of course you can, so long as there is no flirting or anything like that
舞蹈之夜也是一样
That apply to dance nights as well
我们都独自跳舞
We all dance by ourselves
所以我们只放电子音乐
That's why we only play electronic music
你的嘴怎么了
What happened to you mouth
他不能说话 他正在受血吻之刑
He can't speak, he's getting the red kiss
什么是血吻之刑
What's the red kiss?
我们用刀片割掉了他的嘴唇
We slash his lips with razor
以及另一个独身者的嘴唇
and lips of another loner,
然后强迫他们接吻
then force them to kiss each other
几天前的事了
That was couple of days ago now
但是伤口很深 所以他们还处在痛苦中
But the cuts are deep, so they're still in pain
你要知道 他们当时调情来着
They were flirting, you know
惩罚也有好坏之分
Some punishments are worse than other punishments
被切掉拇指可比剃光头要糟糕多了
Having your thumb cut is worse than having you head shaved
在腋窝底下放一颗滚烫的鸡蛋
And having a hot boiled egg under you arm pit...
要比在腿上踢几下更惨
is worse than having you leg kicked
我害怕的惩罚 并不是血吻之刑 而是另一个
The punishment I'm afraid of isn't the red kiss but another one
名叫 血交之刑
It is called the red intercourse
我从来没见过那事发生
I have never seen it happened
但从字面上就能轻易推断出其含义
But it's not difficult to imagine what it is means
我的天哪 我真的很害怕
Oh my God, I'm so afraid of it
跑
Move
躲
Hide
跑
Move
躲
Hide
那是我第一次见到他
That was the first time I saw him
他躲在我身旁一棵树后
He was hiding behind a tree close to mine
他看起来很体面
He seems quite presentable
第二天 在城里
The next day, in the city
他发现我也是近视眼
He found out that I was shortsighted too
那晚在我的梦中 我梦到...
That night in my sleep, I dreamed...
我们同居于城中的一栋大房子里
we lived in a big house together in the city...
房子里有宽敞明亮的厨房
with large and well lit kitchen
我穿着深蓝色的裤子
And I was wearing dark blue trousers...
和紧身的绿色衬衫
and tight green blouse
然后他脱下了我的衣服 跟我做爱
And he took my clothes off and fuck me up the ass
我们正做着的时候 一个歹徒闯进了厨房
And as he was fucking me, a thug came into the kitchen...
从第二个抽屉里拿出了牛排刀
and took the steak knife from the second drawer...
袭击了我们 把刀子捅进了我们的肚子里
and attacked us, stabbing the knife into our belly...
一刀又一刀
one by one
我从噩梦中惊醒
I woke up terrified
再努力些
Try harder
不要放弃 你知道你该更小心些
Don't give up, you know you should've been more careful
再努力一点 不然他们就会发现你
Try harder, or they'll find you...
你就会被变成动物 一只弱小的动物
and you would be turning into a animal, a weak one
我们现在必须得走了
We must get to move on now
待在这实在是太危险了
It's really too dangerous to stay here
如果你能想办法摆脱枷锁 尽力跑 来找我们
If you manage to free yourself, run as fast as you can, and come find us
如果你能摆脱枷锁
If you manage to free yourself,
但觉得自己可能会失血过多而死
but think you'll die from bleeding
那就直接去你的坟墓吧
Go straight to your grave
你挖好自己的坟墓了吗
Have you dug your own grave?
- 挖好了 - 很好
- Yes - Very good
就说到这里
That's enough for now
我要去找松露了
I'm going to go hunting for truffles
他们美味而且稀有
They are delicious and quite rare
一千克能换很多钱
A kilo can fetch a lot of money
那你需要带上一头猪
You're going to need a pig
不然很难找到松露
they are impossible to find out otherwise
- 我知道 - 别去太久
- I know - Don't be long
五十分钟之内 就能采回来
Gonna get them back in 50 minutes
- 你好 大卫 - 你好 罗伯特
- Hello David - Hello Robert
- 你对那个女人好残忍 - 她杀了我的哥哥
- What you did to that woman is dreadful - She killed my brother
如果她杀了你 我也会那么做的
I would've done the same thing if she killed you
你 你对我来说就像兄弟一样
You, you're like a brother to me
你是这个世界上我最好的朋友了
Oh you're my best friend of the whole world
我可不觉得 我是你最好的朋友
I don't think I'm your best friend of the whole world
你以前总和约翰待在一起
You used to spend much time with John
谁是约翰
Oh, who's John?
- 约翰 那个瘸子 - 噢 想起来了
- John, the limping man - Oh yeah
我都记不起他的名字和脸了
I didn't even remember his name, or his face
每当我需要朋友的时候 我只会想起你
You're the one I think of whenever I need a friend
不过 约翰成功了吗
Nevertheless, did John make it?
他们在为游艇之旅做准备了
They're getting ready for the yacht
这周就开始了
All begin this week
所有人都说他们如此般配 肯定会成功的
Everyone said they're going to make it as perfect suited...
而且小孩也能帮他们解决矛盾和争端
and a child could help them pass the fighting and arguing
- 那不错啊 - 你没想过要回来吗
- That's great - You're not thinking coming back?
你要是告诉酒店经理 你哥哥的事
You know if you told the hotel manager about your brother
她可能会原谅你的
She probably forgive you
不了 自己一个人挺好的
No, it's really nice to be on your own
没有人会束缚你
There is no one tying you down
想听歌就听歌 想自慰就自慰
You listen to music whenever you like, You masturbate whenever you want
想散步就散步 想聊天就聊天
Go for a walk whenever you like, have a chat whenever you like
我一点都不想念有人陪伴的日子
I don't miss companionship at all
我只是很想你 因为你是我唯一真正的朋友
I just miss you, because you're my one true friend
你要开枪打我吗
Are you gonna shoot me?
恐怕是的 我只剩两天的时间了
I'm afraid so, I only have two days left
你说什么
What did you said?
我不理解你所说的
I can't understand what you speak
我要开枪打你 我只剩两天的时间了
I'm gonna shoot you, I only have two days left...
我需要更多的时间
and I need more time
你真得相信多一天能有什么不同吗
Do you actually believe another day would make a difference?
你看到自己多丑陋了吗
Have you seen how ugly you are
你没机会的
You haven't got a chance
如果我是个女人...
If I was a woman...
别告诉别人我帮了你
Don't tell anyone I helped you
如果你想回报我 有个办法
If you want to repay me, there is a way
如果你杀了只兔子 就拿来给我吃
If you kill a rabbit, bring it to me to eat
- 你保证吗 - 我保证
- You promise? - Yes
- 再见 - 再见
- Bye - Bye
- 你好 - 你好
- Hello. - Hello.
你带来了我要的东西吗
You brought what I asked for?
当然
Of course
枪在袋子里 里面还有双人房
The gun is in the pocket with the electronic keys...
房号和钥匙
with the numbers of the double rooms.
钥匙不要弄丢了
Try not to lose the keys
我要还回去的
I need to return them
我建议我们周六行动
I propose we act on Saturday...
在舞会之后 大家都累了
after the ball, everyone is tired...
而且大部分员工周末都走了
and most employees are gone on the week-end.
洗发水呢
And the shampoo?
我忘了
I forgot
我下次会带两瓶来
I'll bring two bottles next time
你知道你有多棒吗
Do you know how fantastic you are?
请把洗发水记下来 这样你就不会忘了
Please make a note for the shampoo so you don't forget
我要告诉你点事
I need to tell you something
什么
What?
这是我最后一次任务了
This is my last mission
我不能再这么做了
I can't do it anymore
我受不了继续和那个肥牙医一起
I can't stand living in that horrible mansion...
住在那栋可怕的房子里了
with that fat dentist
他总是问我有没有用牙线
He keeps asking if I've flossed
他让我每吃一次东西之后都清洁牙齿
He makes me clean my teeth after every meal
不管吃得多么少
no matter how small it is
在重要一夜的事宜安排好之后
After we're finished setting up for the big night
你可以来跟我们一起生活
you can come and live with us
我会再找一个内应的
I'll find another mole
我觉得再也找不到像你这样得力的人了
I don't think I'll ever find someone as efficient as you
但我必须尊重你的意愿
but I need to respect your wishes
再耐心等几天
Be patient just a few more days...
不要忘了吃避孕药 好吗
and don't forget to take your birth control pill. Ok?
谢谢
Thank you
不 应该谢谢你
No, thank you
你太棒了
You were fantastic
他小心翼翼地用刀剥了兔子的皮
He carefully flayed the rabbit with sharp knife...
切下了头
and cut off his head
划开了它的肚子
He then sliced open its belly...
在肚子里填满洗净的红椒和青椒
and stuffed with well washed red and green peppers...
不是太辣那种 还放了些大蒜和薄荷
not too spicy, and a little garlic and mint
然后他把肉放到柠檬汁浸泡了一阵
He then soak it to lemon juice and leave it a while to marinate the flesh
再用棍子串起来 放在火上烤一个小时
Before you skewer it on a stick and roast over the fire for about an hour
这就是我最爱吃的东西
That's my favourite food
兔子
Rabbit
女性 深褐色头发 五十岁
Woman, brunette, 50 years old
结婚证书两个月前就过期了
Marriage certificate expired two months ago
- 我丈夫出差去了 - 好吧 我能看看吗
- My husband went on a bussiness trip - Ok, may I have a look?
手伸出来
Hands
她指甲里没有污垢 鞋底也没有泥巴
No dirt under her nails or mud under her shoes
贝尔赛兹大街 九号
9, Belsize road
- 所以你的丈夫确实离开了 - 对
- So your husband does away - Yes
- 去哪了 - 巴斯
- Where? - Bath
早上好 先生
Good morning, sir
你一个人在这吗
Are you here alone?
早上好 警官
Good morning, officer
不 我跟我的伴侣一起来的
No, I'm here with my partner
她现在在其中一家商店购物呢
She's inside one of the stores shopping right now
我能看一下你的证件吗
Can I see you certificate please?
放在我伴侣的钱包里了
My partner keep it in her purse
我自己总是弄丢证件
You see, I'm losing it all the time
好吧 她在哪家店购物呢
I see, and what store is she shopping in?
她来了
Oh, here she is
抱歉 亲爱的
I'm sorry, darling
他们那有太多种类的祛痛膏了
They have such huge variety pain relieve ointment
我给你买了这一种 希望这是你要的那种
I bought you this one, I hope it's the one you're looking for
太好了 亲爱的 能把我的证明给我吗
That's wonderful, dear, can I have my certificate, please?
当然了 亲爱的 您还要看我的证件吗 警官
Of course, darling, would you like to see mine, officer?
不用了
No, that's ok
谢谢 先生
Thank you, sir
祝你一天愉快
You have a good day
- 谢谢 警官 也祝您一天愉快 - 女士
- Thank you, officer, you have a good day - Madam
先生
Sir
如果我走得太慢了 你就直说
If I'm walking too slowly, just say it
我会加快步伐的
And I'll pick up my pace
这个步调挺好的
This pace is fine
但你能别这么用力握我的手嘛
Maybe you don't squeeze my hand so tightly,
我手心都出汗了
my palms are getting a little sweety
- 好些了吗 - 恩 好多了
- Better? - Yes, much better
趁我们还在这 你打算给自己买点好东西吗
Are you planning on buying anything else nice for yourself while we're here?
要买的 隐形眼镜护理液
Yes, contact len solution...
还有派克宝珠笔
and Packer rollerball
我之前不知道你近视
I didn't know you're short-sighted
我也有近视
I'm short-sighted too
你要待几天再走吗
Will you stay a few days?
恐怕不了 爸爸
I'm afraid not, papa
我们今天要回去了
We're heading back again today
明天我要出差去了
tomorrow I'm going away on a bussiness trip
你知道我的工作要求有多高
You know how demanding my job is
不要每次都问我 要不要待几天
Don't ask if I can stay a few days everytime I come
你们都在同一家公司工作吗
Do you all work for the same company?
- 是的 - 是的
- Yes - Yes
我女儿跟我说 那是家非常好的公司
My daughter said to me it's a very fine company
你也这么认为吗
Do you agree?
- 是一家相当不错的公司 - 是的
- It's a rather good company - Yes it is
要我说 是最好的公司之一了
One of the best, I would say
这工作唯一的问题就是 我没有太多时间
The only problem with job is that I don't have much time...
来陪我的妻子和孩子
for my wife and kids
我们有四个美丽的小孩
We have four beautiful children
恭喜
Congratulation
- 谢谢 - 谢谢
- Thank you - Thank you
但就算我们没有小孩
But even if we don't have children
我也不会想要离开我的妻子
I would never dream of leaving my wife
就算只有我们两个人 独自生活
Even if it just two of us, on our own,
我们也会继续旅行
we go on trips
我们可以去意大利的波托菲诺
We go to Portofino in Italy,
夏天还可以去希腊岛
and go to Greek island for the summer
所以 我们之间的感情一直如最初般热烈
So our relationship would be as intense as it was at the start
我非常爱我的妻子
I love my wife so much...
我可以为她去死
I could die for her
我就是这么爱她
That's how much I love her
我们在城里的第一天表现得很好
We first day in the city did great
地中海度假那一部分 真的很棒
That part about holiday destination in the Mediterranean was really brilliant
非常感谢
Thank you very much
你什么时候近视的
When did you become short-sighted?
十六岁的时候
When I was 16
- 你呢 - 十二岁
- You? - When I was 12
你第一副眼镜是什么牌子的
What was maker of your first pair of glasses?
我不记得了
I don't remember
- 你也散光吗 - 是的
- Do you have astigmatism too? - Yes
你要我给你背上涂点
Would you like me to rub some balm...
祛痛膏吗
on your back?
涂在你自己够不着的地方
On the bits you can't reach on you own?
那太好了
I like that
- 这里吗 - 下面一点
- Here? - A little lower please
- 这里吗 - 是的
- Here? - Yes
大家好 祝你们好运
Hello everyone, and good luck
房间号码如下
The room numbers are as follows
306号房 是酒店经理和她的伴侣的房间
Room 306, the hotel manager and her partner
他们的声音都很好听
They both have nice voices
240号房 是一对都爱滑雪的情侣
Room 240, couple who both love to ski
282号房 是一对都爱研究社会科学的情侣
Room 282, couple who both studied social science
幸福游艇上 是一对鼻子都容易出血的情侣
Name of the yacht Bliss, couple prone to nose bleed
你还有你 负责306号房
You and you take 306
你还有你 负责240号房
You and you take 240
你去282号房
You take 282
你们两个 去游艇上
And you two, take the yacht
我能去游艇吗
Can I go to the yacht?
那好吧 那你去游艇
Ok then, you take the yacht
你去282号房
And you take 282
我们三个去经理的房间
And us three will take the manager room
我们有四十分钟的时间
We have 40 minutes
醒醒
Wake up
起来
Get up
去那边坐下
Sit down and sit over there
把手放到身后
Put your hands behind your back
一个篮球的重量在五百五十克到六百五十克之间
A basketball weights between 550 and 650 grams
- 你知道吗 - 不 我不知道
- Did you know that? - No, I didn't know that
好吧
Yes
男女比赛的篮球重量也是不一样的
The weight is different for men's and women's game
但大致都在这个范围内
That's roughly how much it weights
- 你知道排球多重吗 - 不知道 但我想知道
- Do you know how much volleyball weights? - No, but I like to find out
- 晚上好 - 晚上好
- Good evening - Good evening
我有点事要告诉你
I have something to tell you
他的鼻子并不是自己流血的
His nose doesn't really bleed on its own
他会撞墙或者撞硬木头 或别的类似东西
He bangs it against the wall or piece of hard wood, or something like that
又或者是趁你没注意时 用小刀割
Or he cut it with pen knife when you're not looking
你们俩并不合适
You two are not suited
闭嘴
Shut up
爸爸 让他走 我要睡觉了
Dad, tell him to leave, I'm sleepy
我也很确定他T恤上的污渍不是血
And I'm quite sure that stain on his T-shirt isn't blood...
应该是樱桃汁或者番茄酱 或者红色水彩颜料
but cherry juice or tomato ketchup, or red water color paint...
或者是其他类似的东西 或者甜菜根汁
or something like that, or beetroot juice
你爱她吗
Do you love her?
全心全意爱她
With all my heart
你有多爱她 程度从一到十五之间选
How much do you love her? On the scale of 1 to 15
十四
十四真是个令人印象深刻的数字
14 is a very impressive score
他真的很爱她
He love her very much indeed
你觉得我们该杀了谁
Who do you think we should kill?
谁能独自更好地生活下去
Who will be able to live on their own better
给你刀子 妈妈 杀了他
Here is the knife, mom, kill him
你最好趁现在离开
You better get out before you can
好吧
Ok
反正 我来想说的话都说完了
That's all I came to said anyway
你
You?
如果这个女人死了 你可以独自生活下去吗
If this woman die, do you think you manage on you own?
还是你会再发展一段感情
Or will you get involve with someone else?
不 我可以独自生活 但她不行
No, I can live alone, she can't
她不在酒店的时候 我一个人待了好几个小时
I'm on my own for hours when she got out the hotel
我喜欢坐在房间里的感觉
I like sitting in the room...
那感觉让我放松 也让我平静
relaxes me, calms me
我非常喜欢这样
I like it a lot
我完全可以独立生活
I can definitely live on my own
- 不 - 安静
- No! - Be quiet
拿着
Take it
干掉她
Shoot her
不
No
不 不 不
No, no, no
你去哪了
Where were you?
我刚才找你
I was looking for you
我刚才在那些树后面自慰
I was masturbating behind those trees over there
你为什么不去跳舞呢
Why aren't you dancing?
我的腿有点疼
My legs are little sore
你挖了自己的坟墓吗
Did you dig your grave
还没有
Not yet
我不想给你压力
I don't mean to pressure you,
也不想破坏我们欢庆的气氛
or to ruin the mood, now we're celebrating
但你总是要去做的
But at some point you have to do it
别指望有人会为你挖坟墓或者收尸
Don't expect anyone else to dig your grave for you or to carry your corpse
甚至在你尸体上撒些土都别想
Or throw some dirts over you,
现实就是这样
that's about it
明天找个你喜欢的地方
tomorrow find a spot you like,
石头别太多 就可以开始了
where the ground isn't too rocky to make a start
- 好好享受今晚 - 谢谢
- Enjoying the rest evening. - Thank you
他最后一位病人刚离开
As soon as his last patient left,
我就走进他的办公室说
I entered his office and I said to him:
"亲爱的 晚饭好了
"honey, the dinner is ready...
然而 我不知道现在还能不能吃东西
however, I'm not sure I can eat right now...
我有一颗门牙疼得厉害...
one of my front teeth hurts a lot...
能请你帮我看看吗 亲爱的"
can you take a look, please dear?"
"好的 当然 没问题" 他说
"Yes, sure, no problem", he said
然后在他转头的那一瞬间
And the minute he turn his head
我拿起电钻推向他的胸膛
I took the drill and I shoved to his chest
这故事听起来真有趣
That story sounds really interesting...
但我要走了
but I have to leave
我记得我在那棵树旁边放了些电池
I just remember I left some batteries next to tree down there...
我可不想把它们弄丢了
and the last thing I want is to lose them
抱歉
Sorry
- 你抓到了兔子吗 - 不 是别人给我的
- Did you catch rabbits? - No, someone brought me them
- 谁 - 一位朋友
- Who? - A friend of mine
- 你想要一只吗 - 不了
- Do you want one? - No
你不必接受别人的兔子
You don't need to accept rabbits from other people
如果你想要兔子 只要说一声 我会多带点来
If you need more rabbits, just ask, and I'll bring more
抓兔子很难 但我会尽力
Catching rabbit is difficult, but I try to do better
你不需要欠别人的情
There is no need for you to be in debt to the others
非常感谢
Thank you very much
给你带兔子的那个男人 他近视吗
The man who brought you rabbits, is he short-sighted?
不知道 我觉得不是
I don't know, I don't think so
好的
Ok
那树上是一只麻雀吗
Is that a sparrow up that tree?
太远了看不清楚 我觉得不是
Can't really see that far, I don't think so
- 你近视吗 - 不
- Are you short-sighted? - No
- 你说谎 - 我说的实话
- You're lying - It's truth
这上面写的是什么
What does it say here?
YKK
你之前就知道
You knew that already
所有拉链上写的都一样
All zips say the same thing
我没有近视
I'm not short-sighted
不明白为什么你不肯相信我呢
I don't understand why you won't believe me?
我可以清楚地看到你 我以前是名飞行员
I can see you really clearly, I used to be a pilot
你戴了隐形眼镜
You wear contact lenses
我不戴隐形眼镜 我没有近视 我发誓
I don't wear contact lenses, I'm not short-sighted, I swear
你就是 你觉得我傻 看不出来吧
You're, you think I'm a idiot and can't tell
让我看看
Let me see
我想看你的眼睛
I want to see your eyes
向上看
Look up
向上 向上
Up, up,
现在向下看
Look down now
向左看
Look left
向右看
Look right
再向上
Up again
抱歉
I'm sorry
我以为你想耍我
I thought you try to fool me
抱歉
I'm sorry
这次的同步训练 我们必须全神贯注...
For this synchronization exercise, we have to fully concentrate...
因为我们要同时按下播放键
as we both have to press play at the exactly the same time
我们为什么不共用一副耳机呢
Why don't we just use one headset?
因为这才是训练的重点
Because that's the whole point
我们的训练就是为了
This is the exercise for us
让我们达到完全同步
We have to be totally synchronize
好的
Ok
- 我准备好了 - 好的
- I'm ready - Ok
五...
5...
四...
4...
三...
3...
二...
2...
我们发明了一套用于彼此交流的暗号
We developed a code that we can communicate with each other...
既是他人在场 他们也不会知道我们在说什么
even in front of the others without them knowing what we're saying
当我们把头向左转 意思是...
When we turn our heads to the left, it means...
"我爱你胜过世间一切"
"I love you more than anything in the world"
当我们把头向右转 意思是...
When we turn our heads to the right, it means...
"小心 我们有危险"
"Watch out, we're in danger"
刚开始我们要非常小心 以免弄混
We have to be very careful in the beginning not to mix up
"我爱你胜过世间一切"
"I love you more than anything in the world"...
和"小心 我们有危险"
with "watch out, we're in danger"
当我们举起左臂 意思是...
When we raise out left arm, it means...
"我想在你怀里跳舞"
"I want to dance in you arm"
当我们握拳 并置于身后
When we make a fist and put it behind our back
意思是 "我们做爱吧"
It means "Let's fuck"
随着时间的推移 暗号越来越多
The code grew, and grew as the time went by
几周后 我们不需要开口
And within a few weeks, we could talk about almost anything...
就几乎能交流任何事情
without even opening our mouths
停下来
Stop it
够了 请尊重一下我的父母
That's enough, show my parents some respect
他们在为你们演奏
They're playing you music
没关系的
That's ok
不 妈妈 这样不行
No mother, that's not ok
请继续
Please continue
你希望我弹奏同一曲 还是换一曲
Do you want me to play same piece or something else
换一曲吧
Something else
她父母演奏得十分美妙动听 不是吗
Didn't her parents play beautifully?
的确是 很美妙
Yes they did, it was wonderful
我们彼此相爱 而且我们很般配
We love each other, and we suit each other
这就是为什么我们决定离开树林
And that's the reason why we decide to leave the woods...
去城里共度余生
and stay together forever in the city
明天 捕猎时 我们会消失
tomorrow, during the hunt, we're going to disappear...
大家都会以为我们被抓走了
and everyone would think we been captured
然后我们会被改造成狗或者金丝雀什么的
And then we're going to turn into dogs or canary something
到了城里 我想做的第一件事是
I think the first thing I'm going to do when I get into the city...
买件浴袍
is buy a bathrobe
然后我们去泳池 跳水板很高
And then we're going to a pool with high diving board...
非常适合跳水的那种
perfect for diving
我们还要一起做很多事 正经的事 不是蠢事
And then we do lots of different things together, serious thing, not silly one...
比如在公园里散步 或是一起弹吉他...
like go for a walk in the park or play the guitar together...
只写到这里
It stops there
后面还有笔记 但我觉得不重要
There's notes at the back, but I don't think it's important
读读笔记
Read the notes
波托菲诺 意大利渔村
Portofino: Italy fishing village...
高级度假胜地 以风景如画的港湾而出名
upmarket resort famous for its picturesque harbour
人口数为四百三十九
Population: 439
附近的沙滩 帕拉奇 卡莫利 基亚瓦里...
Beachs nearby: Paraggi beach, Camogli, Chiavari...
和拉瓦尼亚
and Lavagna
塞利佛斯岛 希腊岛屿 位于基克拉迪群岛西部
Serifos: Greek island located in the western Cyclades
你在哪找到这笔记的
Where did you find that?
在河边
By the river
有人在捕猎的时候弄丢的
Someone must've dropped it during the hunt
交给我
Give it to me
我来处理
I'll take care of it
知道为什么今天我带你来这么僻静的地方吗
Can you imagine why I brought you to such quiet place today?
不知道
No
因为我觉得 这是个适合安葬你的好地方
Because I think it's the perfect spot for your grave
现在用土盖住自己
Now cover yourself with soil
用手
Use your hands
把脸也盖上
Over your face too
你不想让脸被狗吃了 对吧
You wouldn't want your face to get eaten by dogs, would you?
如果你比我早死
If you die before me,
我会尽我所能多来看望你 我保证
I'll visit you as often as I can, I promise
我觉得我们现在该走了
I think we should leave right now
我们三个来到这里...
The three of us coming here...
而不是两个或者四个 这很危险
in stead of two or four is very dangerous
我们之前怎么没想到呢
How didn't we think it early
医生很有可能会怀疑我们
Highly likely the doctor will suspect us
我建议一有机会就逃走
I suggest that we leave the first chance we get
事实上 现在就是个机会
Right now in the fact
别害怕
Don't be afraid
不会有人怀疑的
No one will suspect a thing
我猜你没料到会有这样的惊喜
I bet you aren't expecting the surprise
- 不是很好吗 - 是的
- Isn't it wonderful? - Yes, it is
但我还是想多考虑几天...
Still I'd like a few days just to think it over so that...
我可以等到...
I could maybe have the surgery...
下次来城里再做手术
when next time come to the city?
还有什么需要考虑的呢
What is that to think about?
看得清楚和近视相比哪个更好 还需要考虑吗
It's better to see clearly, or to be short-sighted? is that it?
这很荒谬 你懂的
That's absurd, you know that
而且 这是最好的眼科医生
Anyway, this doctor is the best there is
非常难预约的
And it's very difficult to get a appointment
我几个月前打电话 才能约到今天
I called him months ago to get him to see you today
- 她瞎了 - 谢谢
- She's blind - Thank you
放下你的刀 站起来
Throw down your knife and stand up
你为什么要弄瞎我
Why did you have to blind me?
你本可以弄瞎他的
You could have blinded him?
我不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about
药物让你神志不清
The drugs are messing with you head
如果我是你 我会更勇敢地面对整件事情
If I were you, I would try and be a little braver about the whole thing
现在起来 把刀给我
And now get up and give me your knife
不然我会打倒你 把刀抢过来
Or I'll hit you and take it by force
我来了
Here I come
我发誓要杀了你
I swear I'll kill you
放开我的头发
Let go of my hair
你弄疼我了
You're hurting me
想想看 如果有人瞎了
Just think that when someone goes blind
其他感知能力会更敏锐
One of other senses is heightened
你也可以在树林里抓只狗 训练他做导盲犬
You could also capture a dog in the woods, and train him to guide you
狗可以做到的 知道吗
Dogs can do that, you know?
我会亲自帮你抓狗的
I'll help you catch a dog myself
现在冷静点 不然我会把你丢在这
Now calm down, or I'm going to leave you here...
我觉得你靠自己是找不到二号碰头点的
and I don't think you'll manage to find meeting of two on your own
你喜欢这景色吗
Are you enjoying the view
当然
Sure
你的手怎么了
What happened to your hand?
我当时在用刀砍树枝...
I was cutting a tree branch with a knife...
不小心把自己割伤了
and I cut myself by accident
你今天看起来很英俊 你剪头发了吗
You look handsome today, did you get you haircut?
谢谢 没有 我没有剪头发
Thank you, no, I didn't get my haircut
我今天是要去剪头发
I'm going to get my haircut today
看我给你带了什么
Look what I brought you?
非常感谢 我饿坏了 正好现在就吃
Oh, thank you so much, I'm so hungry, I'll eat it right away
- 这个大号手电筒 - 抱歉
- It's a big flashlight - Oh, I'm sorry
这么大 我还以为是只兔子
It's so big, I thought it was a rabbit
这是我见过最大的手电筒
The biggest flashlight I've ever seen
你准备好今晚走了吗
Are you ready for tonight
当然
Of course I am
我想和你说点事...
I want to tell you something,..
但你千万别生气
But please don't be angry
好的 怎么了
Ok, what's wrong?
我什么也看不见了
I can't see anything
我瞎了
I'm blind
你在说什么
What do you mean?
我没必要向你隐瞒
There is no point to lying to you
你迟早会发现的
You'll find out soon or later
我们的首领在城里把我弄瞎了
Our leader blinded me in the city
她肯定发现我们相爱了
She must've realised I love you, and you love me...
并且打算一起逃到城里
and we're going to run away to the city together
我很抱歉
I'm sorry
你完全看不见了吗
You can't see at all?
是的 完全看不见
No, not at all
那为什么问我剪头发了没
And why you asked for my haircut?
我刚才说那些...
I was just saying that...
是为了 不让你发现我看不见
so you wouldn't realise I could't see
对不起
I'm sorry
别哭 哭会让眼睛更疼的
Don't cry, crying will make our eyes hurt more
我们会想办法解决的
We'll find a way
你是什么血型的
What blood type are you?
B型
B
我一见到她 就知道她就是我要找的人
From the first time I saw her, I knew she was the one
她微笑着凝视我的双眼
As she stared in my eyes and smiled
她美丽动人的唇色
And her lips were the colour of the roses
宛若河边的玫瑰 娇艳而狂野
That grew down the river, all bloody and wild
你喜欢浆果吗 蓝莓或者黑莓
Do you like berries? blue berries? Black berries?
- 不 不 - 噢
- No, no - Oh
你会弹钢琴吗
Can you play the piano?
不会
No
塑料杯
Plastic cup
对 做得很棒
That's right, very good
你会德语吗
Do you speak German?
不会
No
我可以教你说德语
I could teach you German
至少要学一年 才能进行基本对话
It would take a least a year for you
但仍无法熟练掌握
be able to speak the basic not fluently
所以没意义
So there is no point
德语是世界上最难学的语言之一
You know, German is one of the most difficult language in the world to learn
因为语法复杂
Because its grammar is very complicated
我给你带了点东西
I brought you something
鱼
Fish
第二天 我给她带了朵花
On the second day, I brought her a flower
她是我见过最美丽的女人
She was more beautiful than any woman I'd seen
我问她 "你知道野玫瑰生长在哪里吗...
And I said, "Do you know where the wild roses grow...
如此芬芳 鲜艳而自由生长"
So sweet and scarlet and free?"
- 猕猴桃 - 正确 十个都对了 再来一遍
- Kiwi - That's right, 10 out of 10, then again
我可以亲吻你吗
Can I give you a kiss?
为了陪我解闷 想出这么多的游戏活动
I can't thank you enough for all the activities and games...
我对你真是感激不尽
to keep me company
但你知道我们不能再继续下去了
But you know we can't do that anymore
你想再玩一轮触摸猜物吗
Would you like to play another round of touch, guess thing, win
不了 今天就到这里
No, that's enough for today
而且 我也没有东西给你猜了
In any case, I run out of things to test you with
明天再玩吧 或者改天
Maybe tomorrow, or one of these days
明早怎么样
tomorrow morning?
到时候再说
We'll see
- 再见 - 再见
- Bye - Bye
下午好
Good afternoon
你好吗
How are you?
挺好的
Fine
我饿了
I'm hungry
你都好几天没给我带兔子了
You haven't brought me a rabbit for days,..
或者可以用来触摸猜物的东西
Or things for me to touch and guess
我有个好消息告诉你
I've got good news
我想到了一个好办法
I thought a great idea
你要听吗
Have you a minute?
什么办法
What kind of idea?
我抬起左脚
I raise my left foot
用肘部触膝 轻拍两下
I bring my elbow to my knee, and tap it twice
然后用脚触膝 轻拍三下
I bring my foot to my knee, and tap it three times
然后脸朝下 跪下
And I face down, I knee down
触碰自己左脸 然后脸朝上躺下
I touch my left cheek, and then lie face up
你确定要那样做吗
You're sure you prepare to do that?
是的 当然确定
Yes, of course I'm sure
不然我也不会提出来
I wouldn't propose otherwise
什么时候
When?
明天
Tomorrow
我们得快一点
We should speed up a little
我不能再快了
I can't go much faster
这裤子太紧了 抱歉
These trousers are too tight, I'm sorry
天很黑 我看不清
It was dark, I couldn't see clearly
我也没时间试衣服
And I didn't have time to try them on
抱歉
I'm sorry
没关系
Never mind
公交车来了
There is a bus coming
是酒店的专车
It was the hotel coach
他们没看到我们
They didn't see us
侧脸
Profile
手指
Fingers
手肘
Elbows
你想看我的肚子吗
Would you like me to show you my belly?
不 你的肚子我记得很清楚
No, I remember you belly very well
微笑
Smile
我能要一副刀叉吗
Can I have a knife and fork please?
不是黄油刀 是牛排刀
Not a butter knife, steak knife
稍等
Second
谢谢
Thank you
我准备用刀
I'm going to do with the knife
- 你想要我陪你吗 - 我不希望你去
- Do you want me to come with you? - I rather you didn't
别担心
Don't worry
刚开始有点奇怪 但你会适应的
It's strange at first, but you get used to it
而且你其他感官会变得更灵敏
And you other senses are heightened
例如 触觉 听觉
Touch, for example, and hearing
我知道
I know
我很快就回来
I won't be long
非常感谢
Thank you very much